[
    {
        "Question": "abandoned",
        "Answer": "no longer occupied",
        "Options": "left alone/ give up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "aberrant",
        "Answer": "abnormal",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abolished",
        "Answer": "ended",
        "Options": "eliminated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "abort",
        "Answer": "quit",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abound",
        "Answer": "are numerous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abrupt",
        "Answer": "sudden",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "absorb",
        "Answer": "appeal",
        "Options": "learn/ take in"
    },
    {
        "Question": "abstract",
        "Answer": "not concrete",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "absurd",
        "Answer": "ridiculous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abundant",
        "Answer": "plentiful/ substantial",
        "Options": "ample/ affluent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accelerate",
        "Answer": "speed up",
        "Options": "get faster"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accessible",
        "Answer": "available/ reachable",
        "Options": "easy to obtain"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accidental",
        "Answer": "unintentional",
        "Options": "unexpected"
    },
    {
        "Question": "acclaimed",
        "Answer": "praisable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accomodate",
        "Answer": "provide for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accompany",
        "Answer": "occur along with",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accomplished",
        "Answer": "achieved",
        "Options": "skilled"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accordingly",
        "Answer": "correspondingly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accounts for",
        "Answer": "explains",
        "Options": "describe"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accumulated",
        "Answer": "collected",
        "Options": "gather"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accumulation",
        "Answer": "build up/ deposits",
        "Options": "increasing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accustomed to",
        "Answer": "became used to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "acquire",
        "Answer": "obtain",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adept",
        "Answer": "skillful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adequately",
        "Answer": "sufficiently",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adherent",
        "Answer": "supporter",
        "Options": "advocate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "adjacent to",
        "Answer": "next to/ nearby",
        "Options": "neighboring"
    },
    {
        "Question": "adjust",
        "Answer": "modify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "administer",
        "Answer": "manage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "admirably",
        "Answer": "very well",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "admiration for",
        "Answer": "high opinion of",
        "Options": "respect"
    },
    {
        "Question": "admit",
        "Answer": "let in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "advance",
        "Answer": "improvement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "advantageous",
        "Answer": "beneficial",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "advent",
        "Answer": "arrival",
        "Options": "beginning"
    },
    {
        "Question": "adverse",
        "Answer": "harmful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "advocated",
        "Answer": "promoted",
        "Options": "proponents"
    },
    {
        "Question": "affair",
        "Answer": "matter",
        "Options": "event"
    },
    {
        "Question": "affectional tie",
        "Answer": "emotional attachment",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "afford",
        "Answer": "offer",
        "Options": "provide"
    },
    {
        "Question": "aggravate",
        "Answer": "annoy",
        "Options": "increase"
    },
    {
        "Question": "aggregate",
        "Answer": "combined/ group",
        "Options": "overall"
    },
    {
        "Question": "agile",
        "Answer": "astute/ quick and active",
        "Options": "clever"
    },
    {
        "Question": "air",
        "Answer": "feeling",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "alarm",
        "Answer": "sound",
        "Options": "warning"
    },
    {
        "Question": "albeit",
        "Answer": "though",
        "Options": "even though"
    },
    {
        "Question": "alleged",
        "Answer": "supposed",
        "Options": "asserted"
    },
    {
        "Question": "alliances",
        "Answer": "partnerships",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "allied",
        "Answer": "related",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "allocation",
        "Answer": "distribution",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "allowing",
        "Answer": "enabling",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "allude",
        "Answer": "refer",
        "Options": "suggest"
    },
    {
        "Question": "allusion",
        "Answer": "reference",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ally with",
        "Answer": "link to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "altered",
        "Answer": "transformed",
        "Options": "changed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "alternate",
        "Answer": "take turns at",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "agencies",
        "Answer": "forces",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "agitated",
        "Answer": "created movement in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "a glimpse into",
        "Answer": "a brief view of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "amazing",
        "Answer": "remarkable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ambiguities",
        "Answer": "can be interpreted in more than one way",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ambitious",
        "Answer": "impressive but difficult to achieve",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ambivalent",
        "Answer": "mixed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ample",
        "Answer": "plenty",
        "Options": "spacious"
    },
    {
        "Question": "analogous to",
        "Answer": "similar",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ancestor",
        "Answer": "relative from an earlier generation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ancient",
        "Answer": "antique",
        "Options": "old"
    },
    {
        "Question": "anomaly",
        "Answer": "irregularity",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "annihilate",
        "Answer": "completely remove",
        "Options": "destroy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "annual",
        "Answer": "yearly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "antagonist",
        "Answer": "competitor",
        "Options": "rival"
    },
    {
        "Question": "antagonizing",
        "Answer": "angering",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "anticipate",
        "Answer": "expect",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "antithesis",
        "Answer": "opposite",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "anxiety",
        "Answer": "worry",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "apart from",
        "Answer": "besides",
        "Options": "except for"
    },
    {
        "Question": "apparatus",
        "Answer": "equipment",
        "Options": "device"
    },
    {
        "Question": "apparently",
        "Answer": "seemingly/ obviously",
        "Options": "clearly seen in"
    },
    {
        "Question": "appealing",
        "Answer": "attractive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appearance",
        "Answer": "arrival/ rise",
        "Options": "shown up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "application",
        "Answer": "use",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appraisal",
        "Answer": "evaluation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appreciated",
        "Answer": "approved",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appreciation",
        "Answer": "recognition",
        "Options": "noticeable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "approach",
        "Answer": "come nearer to/ move toward",
        "Options": "method"
    },
    {
        "Question": "appropriate",
        "Answer": "suitable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "approximating",
        "Answer": "estimating",
        "Options": "resembling"
    },
    {
        "Question": "approximately",
        "Answer": "roughtly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "architecture",
        "Answer": "structure",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "archive",
        "Answer": "record",
        "Options": "store"
    },
    {
        "Question": "arduous",
        "Answer": "difficult",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "are preserved",
        "Answer": "survive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "arid",
        "Answer": "dry",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "arise",
        "Answer": "come about ",
        "Options": "emerge"
    },
    {
        "Question": "arrangement",
        "Answer": "configuration",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "array",
        "Answer": "range",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "article",
        "Answer": "item/ object",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "artificial",
        "Answer": "human-made",
        "Options": "not real"
    },
    {
        "Question": "as a rule",
        "Answer": "in general",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ascend",
        "Answer": "go up",
        "Options": "climbing"
    }
]